Perls Galleries
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1937-1995, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-44, OV 81-83; 43.6 linear feet)
  - Witt, Peter N. and Inge, 1961-1963, 1971-1972 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Witte-Külo, Lilo, 1946-1948, 1953-1954 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - WNET/Thirteen, 1979-1990 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Wolf, Edwin D., 1941-1942, 1948, 1965-1970 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Wollman, Milton H., 1959, 1973, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Woods, Andrew C., 1951-1953 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Worcester Art Museum, 1939, 1944-1947, 1952, 1964-1970, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Worden, Frederic G. and Katharine, 1950-1953, 1979-1981, 1987-1988, 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Worthington Gallery, 1977-1980 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Wray, Peter G. and Gay F., 1971-1983 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Wray, Peter G. and Gay F., 1984-1987 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Wünsche, Hermann, 1970-1974 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Wurtzburger, Alan and Janet, 1953, 1958-1961, 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Wurzburger, Paul D., 1962-1971, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Wurzburger, Paul D., 1952-1960 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous W, circa 1937-1995, (17 folders); (see also OV 83) (Box 43, Folder 33-49)
  - Xerox, 1980-1995 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous X, 1941, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Yale University, 1939-1979, 1986, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Yamatane International Inc., 1987-1992 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Yayoi Beoki Co., Ltd., 1978-1979 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Yolanda Gallery, 1984-1987 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - The Yomiuri Shumbun, 1964-1968, 1977-1986 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Yorkville Lumber Co., Inc., 1975-1981 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Yow, Alexander J., 1963-1992 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Y, circa 1937-1995 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Zabriskie Gallery, 1974-1980 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Zacks, Samuel J. and Ayala, 1952-1955, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Zak, Jadia, 1939 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Zidle, Carl J., 1970-1975 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Zilkha, Ezra K., 1974, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Zitman, Cornelis, 1978-1980 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Zuckert, Donald, 1988-1993 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Z, circa 1937-1995, (2 folders) (Box 44, Folder 18-19)
  - Architectural and Engineering Drawings, Posters, (see also Box 8, Folder 59; Box 10, Folders 38 and 41; Box 11, Folder 56; Box 12, Folder 39; Box 15, Folder 27; Box 19, Folder 10; Box 24, Folder 20; Box 26, Folder 24; Box 29, Folder 39; Box 37, Folder 14) (Box OV 81)
  - Architectural and Engineering Drawings, (see also Box 10, Folders 38 and 41; Box 12, Folder 40; Box 19, Folder 10; Box 20, Folder 9; Box 29, Folder 16) (Box OV 82)
  - Architectural and Engineering Drawings, (see also Box 29, Folder 39; Box 31, Folder 3; Box 32, Folder 30; Box 36, Folder 28; Box 43, Folder 44) (Box OV 83)
- Negatives, circa 1937-1995, Series 2:; (Boxes 44-59; 15.7 linear feet)
  Nearly all of the negatives in this series depict artwork from the Perls Galleries inventory. There are at least two negatives depicting Klaus Perls with Alexander Calder in the Perls Galleries (see Box 59, Folder 17). There are two sets of index cards providing access and cross-references to the gallery's numbering system. The blue and green cards list artwork by artist name, geographical region, or African tribe, C-Z - the letters A and B are missing. Yellow cards list artwork by photograph number. The entries on the cards also cross-reference the gallery's stock numbering system.
  The negatives are numbered and arranged according to the gallery inventory numbering system. Many negatives of Calder's artwork were separated, probably for the catalogue raisonné, and filed at the end of the numbered seris.
  - P1-10 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - P11-20 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - P21-30 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - P31-40 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - P41-50 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - P51-60 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - P61-70 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - P71-80 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - P81-90 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - P91-100 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - P101-110 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - P111-120 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - P121-130 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - P131-140 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - P141-150 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - P151-160 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - P161-170 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - P171-180 (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - P181-190 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - P191-200 (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - P201-210 (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - P211-220 (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - P221-230 (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - P231-240 (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - P241-250 (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - P251-260 (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - P261-270 (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - P271-280 (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - P281-290 (Box 44, Folder 48)
  - P291-300 (Box 44, Folder 49)
  - P301-310 (Box 44, Folder 50)
  - P311-320 (Box 44, Folder 51)
  - P321-330 (Box 44, Folder 52)
  - P331-340 (Box 44, Folder 53)
  - P341-350 (Box 44, Folder 54)
  - P351-360 (Box 44, Folder 55)
  - P361-370 (Box 44, Folder 56)
  - P371-380 (Box 44, Folder 57)
  - P381-390 (Box 44, Folder 58)
  - P391-400 (Box 44, Folder 59)
  - P401-410 (Box 44, Folder 60)
  - P411-420 (Box 44, Folder 61)
  - P421-430 (Box 44, Folder 62)
  - P431-440 (Box 44, Folder 63)
  - P441-450 (Box 44, Folder 64)
  - P451-460 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - P461-470 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - P471-480 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - P481-490 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - P491-500 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - P501-510 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - P511-520 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - P521-530 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - P531-540 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - P541-550 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - P551-560 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - P561-570 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - P571-580 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - P581-590 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - P591-600 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - P601-610 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - P611-620 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - P621-630 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - P631-640 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - P641-650 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - P651-660 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - P661-670 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - P671-680 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - P681-690 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - P691-700 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - P701-710 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - P711-720 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - P721-730 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - P731-740 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - P741-750 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - P751-760 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - P761-770 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - P771-780 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - P781-790 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - P791-800 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - P801-810 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - P811-820 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - P821-830 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - P831-840 (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - P841-850 (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - P851-860 (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - P861-870 (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - P871-880 (Box 45, Folder 43)
  - P881-890 (Box 45, Folder 44)
  - P801-900 (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - P901-910 (Box 45, Folder 46)
  - P911-920 (Box 45, Folder 47)
  - P921-930 (Box 45, Folder 48)
  - P931-940 (Box 45, Folder 49)
  - P941-950 (Box 45, Folder 50)
  - P951-960 (Box 45, Folder 51)
  - P961-970 (Box 45, Folder 52)
  - P971-980 (Box 45, Folder 53)
  - P981-990 (Box 45, Folder 54)
  - P991-1000 (Box 45, Folder 55)
  - P1001-1010 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - P1011-1020 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - P1021-1030 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - P1031-1040 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - P1041-1050 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - P1051-1060 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - P1061-1070 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - P1071-1080 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - P1081-1090 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - P1091-1100 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - P1101-1110 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - P1111-1120 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - P1121-1130 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - P1131-1140 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - P1141-1150 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - P1151-1160 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - P1161-1170 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - P1171-1180 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - P1181-1190 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - P1191-1200 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - P1201-1210 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - P1211-1220 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - P1221-1230 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - P1231-1240 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - P1241-1250 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - P1251-1260 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - P1261-1270 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - P1271-1280 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - P1281-1290 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - P1291-1300 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - P1301-1310 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - P1311-1320 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - P1321-1330 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - P1331-1340 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - P1341-1350 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - P1351-1360 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - P1361-1370 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - P1371-1380 (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - P1381-1390 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - P1391-1400 (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - P1401-1410 (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - P1411-1420 (Box 46, Folder 42)
  - P1421-1430 (Box 46, Folder 43)
  - P1431-1440 (Box 46, Folder 44)
  - P1441-1450 (Box 46, Folder 45)
  - P1451-1460 (Box 46, Folder 46)
  - P1461-1470 (Box 46, Folder 47)
  - P1471-1480 (Box 46, Folder 48)
  - P1481-1490 (Box 46, Folder 49)
  - P1491-1500 (Box 46, Folder 50)
  - P1501-1510 (Box 46, Folder 51)
  - P1511-1520 (Box 46, Folder 52)
  - P1521-1530 (Box 46, Folder 53)
  - P1531-1540 (Box 46, Folder 54)
  - P1541-1550 (Box 46, Folder 55)
  - P1551-1560 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - P1561-1570 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - P1571-1580 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - P1581-1590 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - P1591-1600 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - P1601-1610 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - P1611-1620 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - P1621-1630 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - P1631-1640 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - P1641-1650 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - P1651-1660 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - P1661-1670 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - P1671-1680 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - P1681-1690 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - P1691-1700 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - P1701-1710 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - P1711-1720 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - P1721-1730 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - P1731-1740 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - P1741-1750 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - P1751-1760 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - P1761-1770 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - P1771-1780 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - P1781-1790 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - P1791-1800 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - P1801-1810 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - P1811-1820 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - P1821-1830 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - P1831-1840 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - P1841-1850 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - P1851-1860 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - P1861-1870 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - P1871-1880 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - P1881-1890 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - P1891-1900 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - P1901-1910 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - P1911-1920 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - P1921-1930 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - P1931-1940 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - P1941-1950 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - P1951-1960 (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - P1961-1970 (Box 47, Folder 42)
  - P1971-1980 (Box 47, Folder 43)
  - P1981-1990 (Box 47, Folder 44)
  - P1991-2000 (Box 47, Folder 45)
  - P2011-2011 (Box 47, Folder 46)
  - P2012-2020 (Box 47, Folder 47)
  - P2021-2030 (Box 47, Folder 48)
  - P2031-2040 (Box 47, Folder 49)
  - P2041-2050 (Box 47, Folder 50)
  - P2051-2060 (Box 47, Folder 51)
  - P2061-2070 (Box 47, Folder 52)
  - P2071-2080 (Box 47, Folder 53)
  - P2081-2090 (Box 47, Folder 54)
  - P2091-2100 (Box 47, Folder 55)
  - P2101-2110 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - P2111-2120 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - P2121-2130 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - P2131-2140 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - P2141-2150 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - P2151-2160 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - P2161-2170 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - P2171-2180 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - P2181-2190 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - P2191-2200 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - P2201-2210 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - P2211-2220 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - P2221-2230 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - P2231-2240 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - P2241-2250 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - P2251-2260 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - P2261-2270 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - P2271-2280 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - P2281-2290 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - P2291-2300 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - P2301-2310 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - P2311-2320 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - P2321-2330 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - P2331-2340 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - P2341-2350 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - P2351-2360 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - P2361-2370 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - P2371-2380 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - P2381-2390 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - P2391-2400 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - P2401-2420 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - P2421-2430 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - P2431-2440 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - P2441-2450 (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - P2451-2460 (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - P2461-2470 (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - P2471-2480 (Box 48, Folder 37)
  - P2481-2490 (Box 48, Folder 38)
  - P2491-2500 (Box 48, Folder 39)
  - P2501-2510 (Box 48, Folder 40)
  - P2511-2520 (Box 48, Folder 41)
  - P2521-2530 (Box 48, Folder 42)
  - P2531-2540 (Box 48, Folder 43)
  - P2541-2550 (Box 48, Folder 44)
  - P2551-2560 (Box 48, Folder 45)
  - P2561-2570 (Box 48, Folder 46)
  - P2571-2580 (Box 48, Folder 47)
  - P2581-2590 (Box 48, Folder 48)
  - P2591-2600 (Box 48, Folder 49)
  - P2601-2610 (Box 48, Folder 50)
  - P2611-2620 (Box 48, Folder 51)
  - P2621-2630 (Box 48, Folder 52)
  - P2631-2640 (Box 48, Folder 53)
  - P2641-2650 (Box 48, Folder 54)
  - P2651-2660 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - P2661-2670 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - P2671-2680 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - P2681-2690 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - P2691-2700 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - P2701-2710 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - P2711-2720 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - P2721-2730 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - P2731-2740 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - P2741-2750 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - P2751-2760 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - P2761-2770 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - P2771-2780 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - P2781-2790 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - P2791-2800 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - P2801-2810 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - P2811-2820 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - P2821-2830 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - P2831-2840 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - P2841-2850 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - P2851-2860 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - P2861-2870 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - P2871-2880 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - P2881-2890 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - P2891-2800 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - P2801-2910 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - P2911-2920 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - P2921-2930 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - P2931-2940 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - P2941-2950 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - P2951-2960 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - P2961-2970 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - P2971-2980 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - P2981-2990 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - P2991-3000 (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - P3001-3010 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - P3011-3020 (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - P3021-3030 (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - P3031-3040 (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - P3041-3050 (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - P3051-3060 (Box 49, Folder 41)
  - P3061-3070 (Box 49, Folder 42)
  - P3071-3080 (Box 49, Folder 43)
  - P3081-3090 (Box 49, Folder 44)
  - P3091-3100 (Box 49, Folder 45)
  - P3101-3110 (Box 49, Folder 46)
  - P3111-3120 (Box 49, Folder 47)
  - P3121-3130 (Box 49, Folder 48)
  - P3131-3140 (Box 49, Folder 49)
  - P3141-3150 (Box 49, Folder 50)
  - P3151-3160 (Box 49, Folder 51)
  - P3161-3170 (Box 49, Folder 52)
  - P3171-3180 (Box 49, Folder 53)
  - P3181-3190 (Box 49, Folder 54)
  - P3191-3200 (Box 49, Folder 55)
  - P3201-3210 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - P3211-3220 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - P3221-3230 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - P3231-3240 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - P3241-3250 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - P3251-3260 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - P3261-3270 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - P3271-3280 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - P3281-3290 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - P3291-3300 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - P3301-3310 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - P3311-3320 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - P3321-3330 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - P3331-3340 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - P3341-3350 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - P3351-3360 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - P3361-3370 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - P3371-3380 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - P3381-3390 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - P3391-3400 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - P3401-3410 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - P3411-3420 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - P3421-3430 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - P3431-3440 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - P3441-3450 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - P3451-3460 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - P3461-3470 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - P3471-3480 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - P3481-3490 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - P3491-3500 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - P3501-3510 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - P3511-3520 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - P3521-3530 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - P3531-3540 (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - P3541-3550 (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - P3551-3560 (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - P3561-3570 (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - P3571-3580 (Box 50, Folder 38)
  - P3581-3590 (Box 50, Folder 39)
  - P3591-3600 (Box 50, Folder 40)
  - P3601-3610 (Box 50, Folder 41)
  - P3611-3620 (Box 50, Folder 42)
  - P3621-3630 (Box 50, Folder 43)
  - P3631-3640 (Box 50, Folder 44)
  - P3641-3650 (Box 50, Folder 45)
  - P3651-3660 (Box 50, Folder 46)
  - P3661-3670 (Box 50, Folder 47)
  - P3671-3680 (Box 50, Folder 48)
  - P3681-3690 (Box 50, Folder 49)
  - P3691-3700 (Box 50, Folder 50)
  - P3701-3710 (Box 50, Folder 51)
  - P3711-3720 (Box 50, Folder 52)
  - P3721-3730 (Box 50, Folder 53)
  - P3731-3740 (Box 50, Folder 54)
  - P3741-3750 (Box 50, Folder 55)
  - P3751-3760 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - P3761-3770 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - P3771-3780 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - P3781-3790 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - P3791-3800 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - P3801-3810 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - P3811-3820 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - P3821-3830 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - P3831-3840 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - P3841-3850 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - P3851-3860 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - P3861-3870 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - P3871-3880 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - P3881-3890 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - P3891-3900 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - P3901-3910 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - P3911-3920 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - P3921-3930 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - P3931-3940 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - P3941-3950 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - P3951-3960 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - P3961-3970 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - P3971-3980 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - P3981-3990 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - P3991-4000 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - P4001-4010 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - P4011-4020 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - P4021-4030 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - P4031-4040 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - P4041-4050 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - P4051-4060 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - P4061-4070 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - P4071-4080 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - P4081-4090 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - P4091-4100 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - P4101-4110 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - P4111-4120 (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - P4121-4130 (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - P4131-4140 (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - P4141-4150 (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - P4151-4160 (Box 51, Folder 41)
  - P4161-4170 (Box 51, Folder 42)
  - P4171-4180 (Box 51, Folder 43)
  - P4181-4190 (Box 51, Folder 44)
  - P4191-4200 (Box 51, Folder 45)
  - P4201-4210 (Box 51, Folder 46)
  - P4211-4220 (Box 51, Folder 47)
  - P4221-4230 (Box 51, Folder 48)
  - P4231-4240 (Box 51, Folder 49)
  - P4241-4250 (Box 51, Folder 50)
  - P4251-4260 (Box 51, Folder 51)
  - P4261-4270 (Box 51, Folder 52)
  - P4271-4280 (Box 51, Folder 53)
  - P4281-4290 (Box 51, Folder 54)
  - P4291-4300 (Box 51, Folder 55)
  - P4301-4310 (Box 51, Folder 56)
  - P4311-4320 (Box 51, Folder 57)
  - P4321-4330 (Box 51, Folder 58)
  - P4331-4340 (Box 51, Folder 59)
  - P4341-4350 (Box 51, Folder 60)
  - P4351-4360 (Box 51, Folder 61)
  - P4361-4370 (Box 51, Folder 62)
  - P4371-4380 (Box 51, Folder 63)
  - P4381-4390 (Box 51, Folder 64)
  - P4391-4400 (Box 51, Folder 65)
  - P4401-4410 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - P4411-4420 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - P4421-4430 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - P4431-4440 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - P4441-4450 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - P4451-4460 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - P4461-4470 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - P4471-4480 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - P4481-4490 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - P4491-4500 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - P4501-4510 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - P4511-4520 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - P4521-4530 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - P4531-4540 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - P4541-4550 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - P4551-4560 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - P4561-4570 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - P4571-4580 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - P4581-4590 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - P4591-4600 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - P4601-4610 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - P4611-4620 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - P4621-4630 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - P4631-4640 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - P4641-4650 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - P4651-4660 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - P4661-4670 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - P4671-4680 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - P4681-4690 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - P4691-4700 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - P4701-4710 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - P4711-4720 (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - P4721-4730 (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - P4731-4740 (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - P4741-4750 (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - P4751-4760 (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - P4761-4770 (Box 52, Folder 37)
  - P4771-4780 (Box 52, Folder 38)
  - P4781-4790 (Box 52, Folder 39)
  - P4791-4800 (Box 52, Folder 40)
  - P4801-4810 (Box 52, Folder 41)
  - P4811-4820 (Box 52, Folder 42)
  - P4821-4830 (Box 52, Folder 43)
  - P4831-4840 (Box 52, Folder 44)
  - P4841-4850 (Box 52, Folder 45)
  - P4851-4860 (Box 52, Folder 46)
  - P4861-4870 (Box 52, Folder 47)
  - P4871-4880 (Box 52, Folder 48)
  - P4881-4890 (Box 52, Folder 49)
  - P4891-4900 (Box 52, Folder 50)
  - P4901-4910 (Box 52, Folder 51)
  - P4911-4920 (Box 52, Folder 52)
  - P4921-4930 (Box 52, Folder 53)
  - P4931-4940 (Box 52, Folder 54)
  - P4941-4950 (Box 52, Folder 55)
  - P4951-4960 (Box 52, Folder 56)
  - P4961-4970 (Box 52, Folder 57)
  - P4971-4980 (Box 52, Folder 58)
  - P4981-4990 (Box 52, Folder 59)
  - P4991-5000 (Box 52, Folder 60)
  - P5001-5010 (Box 52, Folder 61)
  - P5011-5020 (Box 52, Folder 62)
  - P5021-5030 (Box 52, Folder 63)
  - P5031-5040 (Box 52, Folder 64)
  - P5041-5050 (Box 52, Folder 65)
  - P5051-5060 (Box 52, Folder 66)
  - P5061-5070 (Box 52, Folder 67)
  - P5071-5080 (Box 52, Folder 68)
  - P5081-5090 (Box 52, Folder 69)
  - P5091-5100 (Box 52, Folder 70)
  - P5101-5110 (Box 52, Folder 71)
  - P5111-5120 (Box 52, Folder 72)
  - P5121-5130 (Box 52, Folder 73)
  - P5131-5140 (Box 52, Folder 74)
  - P5141-5150 (Box 52, Folder 75)
  - P5151-5160 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - P5161-5170 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - P5171-5180 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - P5181-5190 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - P5191-5200 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - P5201-5210 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - P5211-5220 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - P5221-5230 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - P5231-5240 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - P5241-5250 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - P5251-5260 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - P5261-5270 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - P5271-5280 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - P5281-5290 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - P5291-5300 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - P5301-5310 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - P5311-5320 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - P5321-5330 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - P5331-5340 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - P5341-5350 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - P5351-5360 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - P5361-5370 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - P5371-5380 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - P5381-5390 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - P5391-5400 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - P5401-5410 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - P5411-5420 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - P5421-5430 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - P5431-5440 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - P5441-5450 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - P5451-5460 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - P5461-5470 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - P5471-5480 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - P5481-5490 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - P5491-5500 (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - P5501-5510 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - P5511-5520 (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - P5521-5530 (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - P5531-5540 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - P5541-5550 (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - P5551-5560 (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - P5561-5570 (Box 53, Folder 42)
  - P5571-5580 (Box 53, Folder 43)
  - P5581-5590 (Box 53, Folder 44)
  - P5591-5600 (Box 53, Folder 45)
  - P5601-5610 (Box 53, Folder 46)
  - P5611-5620 (Box 53, Folder 47)
  - P5621-5630 (Box 53, Folder 48)
  - P5631-5640 (Box 53, Folder 49)
  - P5641-5650 (Box 53, Folder 50)
  - P5651-5660 (Box 53, Folder 51)
  - P5661-5670 (Box 53, Folder 52)
  - P5671-5680 (Box 53, Folder 53)
  - P5681-5690 (Box 53, Folder 54)
  - P5691-5700 (Box 53, Folder 55)
  - P5701-5710 (Box 53, Folder 56)
  - P5711-5720 (Box 53, Folder 57)
  - P5721-5730 (Box 53, Folder 58)
  - P5731-5740 (Box 53, Folder 59)
  - P5741-5750 (Box 53, Folder 60)
  - P5751-5760 (Box 53, Folder 61)
  - P5761-5770 (Box 53, Folder 62)
  - P5771-5780 (Box 53, Folder 63)
  - P5781-5790 (Box 53, Folder 64)
  - P5791-5800 (Box 53, Folder 65)
  - P5801-5810 (Box 53, Folder 66)
  - P5811-5820 (Box 53, Folder 67)
  - P5821-5830 (Box 53, Folder 68)
  - P5831-5840 (Box 53, Folder 69)
  - P5841-5850 (Box 53, Folder 70)
  - P5851-5860 (Box 53, Folder 71)
  - P5861-5870 (Box 53, Folder 72)
  - P5871-5880 (Box 53, Folder 73)
  - P5881-5890 (Box 53, Folder 74)